I've never seen you before.
‫لم أرك من قبل.‬
If you want to do business here, get a state permit first.
‫إن أردت العمل هنا،‬ ‫فاحصل على تصريح حكومي أولًا.‬
Unlicensed prostitutes are trouble.
‫بائعات الهوى غير المرخّصات يجلبن المتاعب.‬
I can't make much money if I do it legally.
‫لا يمكنني أن أجني الكثير من المال‬ ‫إن زاولت العمل بشكل قانوني.‬
Hurry up and go home.
‫أسرعي بالعودة إلى بيتك.‬
If I have his permission, it'll be okay. Right?
‫إن حصلت على إذن منه،‬ ‫فسيكون الأمر على ما يُرام. صحيح؟‬
Let me see him.
‫دعني أقابله.‬
Him? Who are you talking about?
‫هو؟ عمّن تتحدّثين؟‬
I'll keep coming here until you let me see him.
‫سأواصل المجيء إلى هنا‬ ‫حتى تسمح لي بمقابلته.‬
The man they call the "Baby."
‫الرجل الذي يسمّونه "الطفل".‬
You can't use your hands to catch it.
‫لا يمكنك استخدام يديك للإمساك بها.‬
You're not a goalkeeper.
‫أنت لست حارس مرمى.‬
Rules don't apply to me!
‫القواعد لا تنطبق عليّ!‬
Where did he go anyway?
‫أين هو على أي حال؟‬
Who?
‫من؟‬
Tenma, of course!
‫"تينما"، بالطبع!‬
He told me to stay with you for a while
‫أمرني بالبقاء معك لبعض الوقت‬
because he found the man he was looking for.
‫لأنه وجد الرجل الذي كان يبحث عنه.‬
Are you saying that he wants me to look after you?
‫هل تقول إنه يريدني أن أعتني بك؟‬
Hah! Don't be absurd!
‫لا تكن سخيفًا!‬
I hate kids! That Tenma…
‫أكره الأطفال! "تينما"…‬
I couldn't get a hold of him,
‫لم أستطع الاتصال به،‬
and now he's got some mystery kid in tow!
‫والآن جاء ومعه طفل غامض!‬
What happened to our plan of getting rich from him being an underground doctor?
‫ماذا حدث لخطتنا‬ ‫بتحقيق الثراء من عمله كطبيب للمجرمين؟‬
He's got to start working seriously!
‫يجب أن يبدأ العمل بجدّية!‬
Here!
‫خذ!‬
Nice header!
‫ضربة رأسية جميلة!‬
Why you little… What did you do that for? You brat!
‫أيها الصغير…‬
I said you can't touch the ball with your hands.
‫قلت لك إن الإمساك بالكرة ممنوع.‬
A yellow card for you.
‫بطاقة صفراء لك.‬
Shut up! How can I live in this world if I'm scared of that?
‫اصمت! هل تظن أنني أخشى ذلك؟‬
If you keep saying that, you'll get a red card.
‫إن واصلت قول هذا، فستحصل على بطاقة حمراء.‬
Shut up!
‫اصمت!‬
FRANKFURT CENTRAL STATION
‫"محطة (فرانكفورت) المركزية"‬
You're late.
‫تأخرت.‬
Give me the stuff now.
‫أعطني الأغراض الآن.‬
Hurry and give it to me!
‫أسرع وأعطني إياها!‬
It's been a while, Detective Messener.
‫لم أرك منذ فترة أيتها المحقق "ميسنر".‬
D… Doctor Tenma.
‫دكتور "تينما".‬
Yes.
‫أجل.‬
You called me that back then as well,
‫ناديتني بذلك أيضًا في ذلك الوقت،‬
even though we had just met and you never asked what my profession was.
‫رغم أننا كنا قد التقينا للتوّ آنذاك‬ ‫ولم تكن قد سألتني عن مهنتي.‬
However, I'm no longer a doctor.
‫على أي حال، لم أعد طبيبًا.‬
Speaking of which, you are no longer a detective, either.
‫بالحديث عن ذلك، أنت أيضًا لم تعد محققًا.‬
"Officer discharged for possession of narcotics."
‫"ضابط يُصرف من الخدمة لحيازة مخدرات."‬
I was surprised when I found this article from six months ago.
‫فُوجئت حين وجدت هذا المقال قبل ستة أشهر.‬
I'd advise you not to stand up.
‫أنصحك بعدم الوقوف.‬
What?
‫ماذا؟‬
I have a gun pointing at you under my coat.
‫إنني أصوّب نحوك مسدسًا من تحت معطفي.‬
Wh… what do you want?
‫ماذا تريد؟‬
I want to ask you about what you did in Heidelberg ten months ago.
‫أريد أن أسألك عما فعلته في "هايدلبرغ"‬ ‫قبل عشرة أشهر.‬
Also, I want to know who hired you for the job.
‫وأيضًا، أريد أن أعرف من استأجرك‬ ‫لهذه العملية.‬
I… I don't know anything.
‫لا أعرف شيئًا.‬
You took the lives of the Fortners
‫لقد أزهقت أرواح الزوجين "فورتنر"‬
and the journalist, Mr. Maurer.
‫والصحافي، السيد "ماورر".‬
I didn't do it! I was only the lookout.
‫لم أفعل ذلك! لقد راقبت الطريق فحسب.‬
My partner, Müller, did it.
‫زميلي "مولر" هو من قتلهم.‬
Detective Müller quit right after the incident, right?
‫استقال المحقق "مولر"‬ ‫بعد الحادثة مباشرة، صحيح؟‬
Y… Yeah.
‫أجل.‬
He got a lot of money for that and is probably living it up right now.
‫حصل على الكثير من المال مقابل ذلك‬ ‫وعلى الأرجح يعيش حياة مترفة الآن.‬
But you spent all your money on drugs, and this is how you ended up.
‫لكنك أنفقت كل أموالك على المخدرات،‬ ‫وهكذا انتهى بك الأمر.‬
He was the only one who accepted the job and did the deed!
‫كان هو الوحيد الذي قبل أداء المهمة ونفّذها!‬
And he was the one who received most of the payment.
‫وكان هو من تلقّى معظم المبلغ.‬
Someone even once tried to kill me to keep me quiet.
‫حاول أحدهم قتلي مرة لضمان سكوتي.‬
I'm surprised you survived.
‫يدهشني أنك نجوت.‬
I was saved by a certain organization.
‫أنقذتني منظمة معينة.‬
Organization?
‫منظمة؟‬
Isn't this enough? Just leave me be.
‫أليس هذا كافيًا؟ دعني وشأني.‬
I talked too much the other day, too.
‫تكلّمت كثيرًا في ذلك اليوم أيضًا.‬
The other day? To whom?
‫في ذلك اليوم؟ مع من؟‬
Just leave me alone! I don't have time for this.
‫دعني وشأني! ليس لديّ وقت لهذا.‬
You're suffering from withdrawal symptoms.
‫أنت تعاني أعراض الانسحاب.‬
But as long as I'm sitting here,
‫لكنني ما دمت جالسًا هنا،‬
I don't think the dealer will come near you.
‫فلا أظن أن التاجر سيقترب منك.‬
I… I told you!
‫أخبرتك!‬
I was saved by the Baby!
‫أنقذني "الطفل"!‬
"The Baby"?
‫"الطفل"؟‬
Go to the bar called "Candy."
‫اذهب إلى الحانة المسمّاة "كاندي".‬
Then you will meet him there.
‫ستقابله هناك.‬
Who is the "Baby"?
‫من هو "الطفل"؟‬
He's a major far-right figure.
‫إنه شخصية يمينية متطرفة.‬
He has a role in two rightist parties.
‫له دور في حزبين يمينيين.‬
The Baby went to the east side after the Wall fell,
‫ذهب "الطفل" إلى الجانب الشرقي‬ ‫بعد سقوط الجدار،‬
and he tried to build a town of pure Germans.
‫وحاول بناء بلدة من الألمان الأصوليين.‬
But he failed, so he came back here.
‫لكنه فشل، فعاد إلى هنا.‬
Why did that man save you?
‫لماذا أنقذك ذلك الرجل؟‬
The darkness…
‫الظلام…‬
When the Berlin Wall fell, a great darkness was born.
‫حين سقط جدار "برلين"، وُلد ظلام عظيم.‬
A monster… was born.
‫وُلد وحش.‬
Monster?
‫وحش؟‬
Just go away! I told that girl everything already.
‫ارحل فحسب!‬ ‫أخبرت تلك الفتاة بكل شيء بالفعل.‬
That girl?
‫الفتاة؟‬
She came for revenge and pointed a gun at me!
‫جاءت لتنتقم ووجّهت مسدسًا نحوي!‬
She's the daughter of the couple we killed!
‫إنها ابنة الزوجين اللذين قتلناهما!‬
Anna?
‫"آنا"؟‬
Nina…
‫"نينا"…‬
Did Nina Fortner come to see you?
‫هل جاءت "نينا فورتنر" لرؤيتك؟‬
The Baby told me
‫أخبرني "الطفل"‬
if that girl came to me,
‫بأنه إن جاءتني فتاة،‬
I have to tell her to go see him.
‫يجب أن أخبرها بأن تذهب لرؤيته.‬
He said the girl is an important bait.
‫قال إن الفتاة طُعم مهم.‬
An important… bait?
‫طُعم مهم؟‬
You again?
‫أنت مجددًا؟‬
You do have patience, coming here every night.
‫كم أنت صبورة إذ تأتين إلى هنا كل ليلة.‬
How about I buy you for the night at a good price?
‫ما رأيك في أن أشتريك الليلة بسعر جيد؟‬
You said I'd be in trouble if I worked here
‫قلت إنني سأقع في ورطة إن عملت هنا‬
without the Baby's approval.
‫من دون موافقة "الطفل".‬
Why you little!
‫أيتها الملعونة الصغيرة!‬
What the hell is that look?
‫ما هذه النظرة؟‬
Is she the one who wanted to see the Baby?
‫هل هي من أرادت مقابلة "الطفل"؟‬
Uh… Yes.
‫أجل.‬
This way, please.
‫تفضّلي من هنا.‬
Please come with me.
‫تعالي معي من فضلك.‬
Please wait over there.
‫انتظري هناك من فضلك.‬
Please stand on the mark and wait.
‫قفي عند العلامة وانتظري من فضلك.‬
No, no. Right over it.
‫لا. فوقها مباشرة.‬
Yes, that's right.
‫أجل، هذا صحيح.‬
Do you know this song?
‫هل تعرفين هذه الأغنية؟‬
You can't help but feel like dancing to the pleasant rhythm.
‫لا يسعك إلا أن تشعري برغبة في الرقص‬ ‫على الإيقاع اللطيف.‬
Miss Nina Fortner.
‫آنسة "نينا فورتنر".‬
The Baby said it himself.
‫"الطفل" قال ذلك بنفسه.‬
This country would be fine if only a second Hitler was born.
‫لن يكون هذا البلد بخير‬ ‫إلا إذا وُلد "هتلر" ثان.‬
That girl is the bait.
‫تلك الفتاة هي الطُعم.‬
Nina!
‫"نينا"!‬
How did you know my name?
‫كيف عرفت اسمي؟‬
I know everything.
‫أنا أعرف كل شيء.‬
You had another name, Anna Liebert.
‫كان لك اسم آخر، "آنا ليبرت".‬
But that's not your real name, either.
‫لكنه ليس اسمك الحقيقي كذلك.‬
Names have so very little meaning.
‫الأسماء لا معنى لها.‬
After all, my name is the Baby.
‫في النهاية، اسمي "الطفل".‬
Come on and dance.
‫تعالي وارقصي.‬
I heard that you know where I can find my brother.
‫سمعت بأنك تعرف أين يمكنني العثور على أخي.‬
Ah, Johan? That's a good name.
‫"يوهان"؟ هذا اسم جميل.‬
So you do know?
‫إذًا هل تعرف؟‬
I have to kill him.
‫يجب أن أقتله.‬
Please don't wave a dangerous thing like that around.
‫أرجوك ألّا تلوّحي بشيء خطير كهذا.‬
Don't worry.
‫لا تقلقي.‬
I'm sure Johan will show up to see you.
‫أنا واثق بأن "يوهان" سيأتي لرؤيتك.‬
Since I used to live here when I was a kid,
‫بما أنني كنت أعيش هنا في طفولتي،‬
I even know the back alleys in this area.
‫فأنا أعرف الأزقّة الخلفية في المنطقة.‬
There is a pawn shop ahead.
‫هناك متجر رهن.‬
We will pawn this carpet for some cash.
‫سنرهن هذه السجادة مقابل بعض المال.‬
What? You don't have money, Mr. Heckel?
‫ماذا؟ أليس معك نقود يا سيد "هيكل"؟‬
Shut up! I have got to do something to get money for your dinner.
‫اصمت! يجب أن أفعل شيئًا‬ ‫لأحصل على المال حتى أشتري لك العشاء.‬
You should be grateful!
‫يجب أن تكون ممتنًا!‬
Huh?
‫ماذا؟‬
What the…?
‫ما هذا؟‬
What's wrong?
‫ما الخطب؟‬
This area has become a Turkish district.
‫أصبحت هذه المنطقة حيًا تركيًا.‬
This is fake.
‫إنها مزيفة.‬
What… What are you talking about?
‫ماذا؟ عمّ تتحدّث؟‬
Look at this pattern and texture. This is hand-woven silk, for sure!
‫انظر إلى هذا النمط والملمس.‬ ‫هذا حرير منسوج يدويًا بالتأكيد!‬
No, this is synthetic.
‫لا، هذا اصطناعي.‬
Since I feel sorry for you, I'll take it for 100 marks.
‫بما أنني أشفق عليك،‬ ‫فسآخذها مقابل 100 مارك.‬
This is why I hate this.
‫لهذا أكره هذا الوضع.‬
If this store was still owned by a German, I would've got 10,000 marks!
‫لو كان هذا المتجر لا يزال ملكًا لألماني،‬ ‫لحصلت على عشرة آلاف مارك!‬
Then take it back.
‫إذًا خذها.‬
After I'm gone,
‫بعد رحيلي،‬
don't come looking for me when you realize it's real!
‫لا تأت للبحث عني حين تتبيّن أنها أصلية!‬
This is what a real one should look like.
‫هكذا تبدو السجادة الأصلية.‬
This is a 100% silk Hereke carpet.
‫هذه سجادة "هيركيه"‬ ‫مصنوعة من الحرير بنسبة 100 بالمئة.‬
Take a closer look at it.
‫أمعن النظر إليها.‬
Even the small, fine details are elegantly done.
‫حتى التفاصيل الصغيرة الدقيقة متقنة الصنع.‬
It's worth 150,000 marks.
‫قيمتها 150 ألف مارك.‬
That has to be fake!
‫لا بد أنها مزيفة!‬
You don't even have the expertise to see that my carpet is real!
‫أنت لا تملك الخبرة لترى أن سجادتي أصلية!‬
Let's go, Dieter.
‫لنذهب يا "ديتر".‬
Hey, I'm hungry.
‫أنا جائع.‬
-It was real. -Huh?
‫كانت أصلية.‬
That was the real thing, and it's worth 150,000 marks?
‫تلك السجادة أصلية، وقيمتها 150 ألف مارك؟‬
If we know where to sell it, we could get 800,000 marks!
‫إن عرفنا أين نبيعها،‬ ‫فقد نحصل على 800 ألف مارك!‬
Let's eat something.
‫لنأكل شيئًا.‬
Shut up! Once we get that thing,
‫اصمت! حالما نأخذها،‬
we will get to eat whatever we want!
‫سنأكل كل ما نريده!‬
How are you going to get it?
‫كيف سنأخذها؟‬
Let me handle it.
‫دعني أتولى الأمر.‬
Wh… Why are you looking at me like that?
‫ما الأمر؟ لماذا تنظر إليّ هكذا؟‬
You're a thief!
‫أنت لص!‬
Hey, stupid! Keep it down, you brat!
‫أيها الغبي! اخفض صوتك أيها المشاكس!‬
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
‫مهلًا! ماذا تحسب نفسك فاعلًا؟‬
Sorry, but look for other clients.
‫آسف، لكن ابحثي عن زبائن آخرين.‬
That's not it.
‫الأمر ليس كذلك.‬
An Asian man like you wandering around here
‫تجوّل رجل آسيوي مثلك في هذه المنطقة‬
could get killed.
‫قد يعرّضك إلى القتل.‬
That place is a base for right-wing people.
‫هذا المكان معقل لليمينيين.‬
Aren't you Turkish?
‫ألست تركية؟‬
Can you do your business around here?
‫هل تستطيعين مزاولة عملك هنا؟‬
What the hell are you talking about? Why would I work in this dump?
‫عمّ تتحدّث؟ لماذا أعمل في هذا المكان القذر؟‬
My friend was taken by the men in there.
‫الرجال الموجودون بالداخل اختطفوا صديقتي.‬
Apparently, she found out a secret about them.
‫يبدو أنها اكتشفت سرًا عنهم.‬
A secret?
‫سرّ؟‬
I don't know what it was.
‫لا أعرف ما هو.‬
I have to get her out of there. I'm afraid of what they're doing to her.
‫يجب أن أخرجها من هناك.‬ ‫أخشى ما يفعلونه بها.‬
A woman I know is in there too.
‫امرأة أعرفها هناك أيضًا.‬
What kind of woman? Is it a girl with long blonde hair?
‫أي امرأة؟ أهي فتاة ذات شعر أشقر طويل؟‬
I'm not sure what kind of hair she has now.
‫لا أعرف كيف أصبح شعرها حاليًا.‬
If it's her, then she was just taken away in a car.
‫إن كانت هي، فقد أُخذت للتوّ في سيارة.‬
What? Where?
‫ماذا؟ إلى أين؟‬
I don't know.
‫لا أعرف.‬
But the Baby was with her, so she's probably at his house.
‫لكن كان "الطفل" معها،‬ ‫أي أنها على الأرجح في منزله.‬
The Baby?
‫"الطفل"؟‬
What kind of car was it? What color?
‫ما طراز السيارة؟ ما لونها؟‬
It was a big, bright red Mercedes.
‫كانت سيارة "مرسيدس" كبيرة‬ ‫حمراء فاقعة اللون.‬
Good. I'll just have to find the car and go after them.
‫جيد. يجب أن أجد السيارة وألحق بهما.‬
Please save my friend, too!
‫أرجوك أن تنقذ صديقتي أيضًا!‬
Please! She has a little child waiting for her at home.
‫أرجوك! لها طفل صغير ينتظرها في المنزل.‬
I beg of you!
‫أتوسل إليك!‬
What? Not dead, I see.
‫ماذا؟ أرى أنك لم تمت.‬
This way, please.
‫تفضّلي من هنا.‬
Before you go in, let me take your gun.
‫قبل أن تدخلي، دعيني آخذ مسدسك.‬
Now, please go in.
‫والآن، تفضّلي بالدخول.‬
Sit wherever you like.
‫اجلسي أينما تريدين.‬
Are you the girl the Baby brought here?
‫هل أنت الفتاة التي أحضرها "الطفل" إلى هنا؟‬
Let me see your face.
‫دعيني أرى وجهك.‬
Ah, you're quite a beautiful girl indeed.
‫أنت فتاة جميلة بالفعل.‬
It's not a surprise, since you're Johan's twin sister.
‫هذه ليست مفاجأة،‬ ‫بما أنك أخت "يوهان" التوأم.‬
I am Professor Goedelitz.
‫أنا الأستاذ "غوديليتز".‬
The one in the photo with Johan is General Wolf.
‫الشخص الذي يظهر في الصورة مع "يوهان"‬ ‫هو الجنرال "وولف".‬
How about fruit? Would you like some?
‫ماذا عن الفاكهة؟ هل تريدين؟‬
My brother… Please let me see Johan.
‫أخي. أرجوك أن تدعني أرى "يوهان".‬
Once he knows that you're here, he will definitely come.
‫بمجرد أن يعرف أنك هنا، سيأتي بالتأكيد.‬
He needs you.
‫إنه بحاجة إليك.‬
I suppose you don't know where Johan is.
‫أفترض أنك لا تعرف مكان "يوهان".‬
We need him.
‫نحن نحتاج إليه.‬
We need him to be at the top.
‫نحتاج إليه على القمة.‬
Do you know why Hitler was able to have so much power?
‫هل تعرفين لماذا استطاع "هتلر"‬ ‫امتلاك كل هذه القوة؟‬
He was smart, with a mind for business.
‫لأنه كان ذكيًا وصاحب عقلية رجل أعمال.‬
He understood these three points.
‫لقد فهم هذه النقاط الثلاث.‬
He controlled the banks, won over the arms industry, and seized the military.
‫سيطر على المصارف وضمّ إلى صفّه صناعة الأسلحة‬ ‫واستولى على الجيش.‬
Right now, Johan is lying in wait within one of those.
‫حاليًا، "يوهان" ينتظر‬ ‫بداخل أحد تلك المؤسسات.‬
How about it? Don't you think my reasoning is correct?
‫ما رأيك؟ ألا تظنين أن منطقي صحيح؟‬
What will you do with Johan?
‫ماذا ستفعلون بـ"يوهان"؟‬
However, it was Hitler's charisma that allowed him to achieve it all.
‫لكن شخصية "هتلر" الجذابة‬ ‫هي ما أتاحت له تحقيق كل شيء.‬
Hitler failed to get into art school,
‫فشل "هتلر" في الالتحاق بكلية الفنون،‬
then couldn't advance beyond corporal in the military.
‫وبعد ذلك لم يستطع الترقّي‬ ‫لأكثر من رتبة عريف في الجيش.‬
He finally revealed his charisma, only after the age of thirty.
‫تجلّت أخيرًا جاذبية شخصيته‬ ‫بعدما تجاوز الـ30.‬
But what about Johan?
‫لكن ماذا عن "يوهان"؟‬
Ever since he was a child, he had enormous charisma.
‫منذ أن كان طفلًا،‬ ‫يتمتع بجاذبية شخصية هائلة.‬
Almost like another Jesus Christ.
‫وكأنه "مسيح" آخر.‬
But you must not forget one thing.
‫لكن يجب ألّا تنسي شيئًا واحدًا.‬
The first ones to put faith in Christ were the Three Magi
‫أول من رسّخا الإيمان في "المسيح"‬ ‫كانوا "المجوس الثلاثة"،‬
and John the Baptist, four amazing people.
‫و"يوحنا المعمدان"، وهم أربعة أشخاص مذهلون.‬
The four of us have paid close attention to Johan's talent since his childhood.
‫نحن الأربعة نولي اهتمامًا كبيرًا‬ ‫لموهبة "يوهان" منذ طفولته.‬
Isn't that wonderful?
‫أليس هذا رائعًا؟‬
What do you want me to do?
‫ماذا تريدني أن أفعل؟‬
I'd like you to stay here for a while
‫أريدك أن تبقي هنا لفترة‬
until Johan comes to see you.
‫حتى يأتي "يوهان" لرؤيتك.‬
since you have already stepped one foot in.
‫بما أنك قد دخلت بالفعل.‬
You don't have to worry about that. I'm here because I want to.
‫لا داعي للقلق بشأن ذلك. أنا هنا بإرادتي.‬
I'll wait for Johan.
‫سأنتظر "يوهان".‬
That'd be good.
‫سيكون هذا جيدًا.‬
Please, have some fruit.
‫أرجوك، تناولي الفاكهة.‬
I see you have finally come around.
‫أراك قد استعدت وعيك أخيرًا.‬
You don't have to worry.
‫لا داعي للقلق.‬
You don't have any broken bones.
‫ليس لديك أي عظام مكسورة.‬
What are you doing around here?
‫ماذا تفعل هنا؟‬
Dr. Tenma?
‫يا دكتور "تينما"؟‬
How do you know my name?
‫كيف عرفت اسمي؟‬
I'm the one asking questions.
‫أنا من يطرح الأسئلة.‬
You only have to answer.
‫ما عليك سوى الإجابة.‬
What were you trying to do?
‫ماذا كنت تحاول أن تفعل؟‬
What are you going to do after you find Johan?
‫ماذا ستفعل بعدما تجد "يوهان"؟‬
Where is Nina?
‫أين "نينا"؟‬
I told you I'm the one asking the questions.
‫أخبرتك بأنني أنا من يطرح الأسئلة.‬
What are you doing with Nina?
‫ماذا تفعلون بـ"نينا"؟‬
I already said no questions from you!
‫سبق أن قلت إنك لا تطرح الأسئلة!‬
Nina is our important guest.
‫"نينا" ضيفتنا المهمة.‬
She's not trash like you.
‫ليست حثالة مثلك.‬
Then she's fine.
‫إذًا فهي بخير.‬
For now.
‫حاليًا.‬
But that girl is dangerous.
‫لكن تلك الفتاة خطرة.‬
She has such a pretty face, but she's trying to kill Johan.
‫وجهها جميل، لكنها تريد أن تقتل "يوهان".‬
Those kinds of people have to be disposed of eventually.
‫يجب التخلّص من أمثالها في النهاية.‬
So Nina is just a bait to lure Johan, huh?
‫إذًا "نينا" مجرد طُعم‬ ‫لاستدراج "يوهان"، صحيح؟‬
Who are you people?
‫من أنتم؟‬
What are you doing--
‫ماذا تفعلون…‬
Another question?
‫سؤال آخر؟‬
You foreign races have no right to ask questions!
‫أنتم يا أبناء الأعراق الأجنبية‬ ‫لا يحقّ لكم طرح الأسئلة!‬
That kind of impertinent attitude will send this whole district up in flames!
‫هذا التصرف الوقح سيشعل الحي بأكمله!‬
The… district?
‫الحي؟‬
Yes. The sky tomorrow night will be dyed with a beautiful color.
‫أجل. ليلة الغد ستصطبغ السماء بلون جميل.‬
Help…
‫النجدة…‬
Please help me.
‫أرجوكم أن تساعدوني.‬
Who are you?
‫من أنت؟‬
He… Help me.
‫ساعديني.‬
Where are you?
‫أين أنت؟‬
The third floor.
‫الطابق الثالث.‬
You speak in broken German. Where are you from?
‫لديك لكنة غير ألمانية. من أين أنت؟‬
I'm Turkish… They will kill me.
‫أنا تركية. سيقتلونني.‬
I have to run.
‫يجب أن أهرب.‬
I suppose the people here have imprisoned you here.
‫أفترض أن الموجودين هنا قد سجنوك.‬
Help.
‫ساعديني.‬
But I have to stay here.
‫لكنني يجب أن أبقى هنا.‬
Please help.
‫أرجوك أن تساعديني.‬
Someone needs to warn them soon, or else my son will die.
‫يجب تحذيرهم بسرعة، وإلا سيموت ابني.‬
Tomorrow night, we are having a welcome party for Johan.
‫ليلة الغد، سنقيم حفل ترحيب لـ"يوهان".‬
Superior races like ours should be the only ones to exist in this world.
‫يجب ألّا يكون في هذا العالم‬ ‫سوى الأجناس المتفوّقة مثلنا.‬
The rest can all be burned.
‫يمكن إحراق باقي الأجناس.‬
I accidentally overheard the men talking.
‫سمعت الرجال يتحدثون بطريق الصدفة.‬
They're going to start a fire tomorrow night.
‫سيشعلون حريقًا ليلة الغد.‬
They're planning to burn down the Turkish District.
‫إنهم يخططون لإحراق الحي التركي.‬
Help! Help!
‫النجدة!‬